[
  {
    "Number": 1,
    "Question": "What is 1 foot 2 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 0.35,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 2,
    "Question": "What is 1 foot 4 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 0.4,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 3,
    "Question": "What is 1 foot 6 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 0.45,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 4,
    "Question": "What is 1 foot 8 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 0.5,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 5,
    "Question": "What is 1 foot 10 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 0.55,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 6,
    "Question": "What is 2 feet 2 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 0.65,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 7,
    "Question": "What is 2 feet 4 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 0.7,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 8,
    "Question": "What is 2 feet 6 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 0.75,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 9,
    "Question": "What is 2 feet 8 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 0.8,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 10,
    "Question": "What is 2 feet 10 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 0.85,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 11,
    "Question": "What is 3 feet 2 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 0.95,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 12,
    "Question": "What is 3 feet 4 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 13,
    "Question": "What is 3 feet 6 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.05,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 14,
    "Question": "What is 3 feet 8 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.1,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 15,
    "Question": "What is 3 feet 10 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.15,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 16,
    "Question": "What is 4 feet 2 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.25,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 17,
    "Question": "What is 4 feet 4 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.3,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 18,
    "Question": "What is 4 feet 6 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.35,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 19,
    "Question": "What is 4 feet 8 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.4,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 20,
    "Question": "What is 4 feet 10 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.45,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 21,
    "Question": "What is 5 feet 2 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.55,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 22,
    "Question": "What is 5 feet 4 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.6,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 23,
    "Question": "What is 5 feet 6 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.65,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 24,
    "Question": "What is 5 feet 8 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.7,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 25,
    "Question": "What is 5 feet 10 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.75,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 26,
    "Question": "What is 6 feet 2 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.85,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 27,
    "Question": "What is 6 feet 4 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.9,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 28,
    "Question": "What is 6 feet 6 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 1.95,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 29,
    "Question": "What is 6 feet 8 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 2,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 30,
    "Question": "What is 6 feet 10 inches in metres? <strong>(Assume 1 inch = 2.5 cm)</strong>",
    "Answer": 2.05,
    "Units": "m"
  },
  {
    "Number": 31,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 1 lb in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 56.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 32,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 2 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 57,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 33,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 3 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 57.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 34,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 4 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 58,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 35,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 5 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 58.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 36,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 6 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 59,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 37,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 7 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 59.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 38,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 8 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 39,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 9 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 60.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 40,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 10 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 61,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 41,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 11 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 61.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 42,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 12 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 62,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 43,
    "Question": "What is 8 stone 13 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 62.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 44,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 1 lb in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 63.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 45,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 2 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 64,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 46,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 3 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 64.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 47,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 4 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 65,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 48,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 5 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 65.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 49,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 6 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 66,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 50,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 7 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 66.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 51,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 8 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 67,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 52,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 9 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 67.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 53,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 10 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 68,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 54,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 11 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 68.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 55,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 12 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 69,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 56,
    "Question": "What is 9 stone 13 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 69.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 57,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 1 lb in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 70.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 58,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 2 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 71,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 59,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 3 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 71.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 60,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 4 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 72,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 61,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 5 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 72.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 62,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 6 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 73,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 63,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 7 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 73.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 64,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 8 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 74,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 65,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 9 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 74.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 66,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 10 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 67,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 11 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 75.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 68,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 12 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 76,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 69,
    "Question": "What is 10 stone 13 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 76.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 70,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 1 lb in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 77.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 71,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 2 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 78,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 72,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 3 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 78.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 73,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 4 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 79,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 74,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 5 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 79.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 75,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 6 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 76,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 7 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 80.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 77,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 8 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 81,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 78,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 9 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 81.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 79,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 10 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 82,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 80,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 11 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 82.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 81,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 12 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 83,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 82,
    "Question": "What is 11 stone 13 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 83.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 83,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 1 lb in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 84.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 84,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 2 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 85,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 85,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 3 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 85.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 86,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 4 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 86,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 87,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 5 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 86.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 88,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 6 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 87,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 89,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 7 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 87.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 90,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 8 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 88,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 91,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 9 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 88.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 92,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 10 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 89,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 93,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 11 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 89.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 94,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 12 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 95,
    "Question": "What is 12 stone 13 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 90.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 96,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 1 lb in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 91.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 97,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 2 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 92,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 98,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 3 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 92.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 99,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 4 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 93,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 100,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 5 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 93.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 101,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 6 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 94,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 102,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 7 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 94.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 103,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 8 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 104,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 9 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 95.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 105,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 10 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 96,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 106,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 11 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 96.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 107,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 12 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 97,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 108,
    "Question": "What is 13 stone 13 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 97.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 109,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 1 lb in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 98.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 110,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 2 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 99,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 111,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 3 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 99.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 112,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 4 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 113,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 5 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 100.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 114,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 6 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 101,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 115,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 7 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 101.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 116,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 8 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 102,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 117,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 9 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 102.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 118,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 10 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 103,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 119,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 11 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 103.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 120,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 12 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 104,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 121,
    "Question": "What is 14 stone 13 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 104.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 122,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 1 lb in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 105.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 123,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 2 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 106,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 124,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 3 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 106.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 125,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 4 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 107,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 126,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 5 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 107.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 127,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 6 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 108,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 128,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 7 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 108.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 129,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 8 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 109,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 130,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 9 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 109.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 131,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 10 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 132,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 11 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 110.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 133,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 12 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 111,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 134,
    "Question": "What is 15 stone 13 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 111.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 135,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 1 lb in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 112.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 136,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 2 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 113,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 137,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 3 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 113.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 138,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 4 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 114,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 139,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 5 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 114.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 140,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 6 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 115,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 141,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 7 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 115.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 142,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 8 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 116,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 143,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 9 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 116.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 144,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 10 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 117,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 145,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 11 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 117.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 146,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 12 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 118,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 147,
    "Question": "What is 16 stone 13 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 118.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 148,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 1 lb in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 119.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 149,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 2 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 150,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 3 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 120.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 151,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 4 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 121,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 152,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 5 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 121.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 153,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 6 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 122,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 154,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 7 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 122.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 155,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 8 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 123,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 156,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 9 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 123.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 157,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 10 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 124,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 158,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 11 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 124.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 159,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 12 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 125,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 160,
    "Question": "What is 17 stone 13 lbs in kg? <strong>(Assume 1 kg = 2 lbs)</strong>",
    "Answer": 125.5,
    "Units": "kg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 161,
    "Question": "What is 33.8 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 1,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 162,
    "Question": "What is 35.6 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 2,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 163,
    "Question": "What is 37.4 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 164,
    "Question": "What is 39.2 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 4,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 165,
    "Question": "What is 41 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 166,
    "Question": "What is 42.8 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 6,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 167,
    "Question": "What is 44.6 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 7,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 168,
    "Question": "What is 46.4 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 8,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 169,
    "Question": "What is 48.2 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 170,
    "Question": "What is 50 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 171,
    "Question": "What is 51.8 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 11,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 172,
    "Question": "What is 53.6 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 12,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 173,
    "Question": "What is 55.4 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 13,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 174,
    "Question": "What is 57.2 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 14,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 175,
    "Question": "What is 59 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 15,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 176,
    "Question": "What is 60.8 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 16,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 177,
    "Question": "What is 62.6 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 17,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 178,
    "Question": "What is 64.4 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 18,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 179,
    "Question": "What is 66.2 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 19,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 180,
    "Question": "What is 68 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 181,
    "Question": "What is 69.8 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 21,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 182,
    "Question": "What is 71.6 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 22,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 183,
    "Question": "What is 73.4 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 23,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 184,
    "Question": "What is 75.2 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 24,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 185,
    "Question": "What is 77 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 25,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 186,
    "Question": "What is 78.8 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 26,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 187,
    "Question": "What is 80.6 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 27,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 188,
    "Question": "What is 82.4 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 28,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 189,
    "Question": "What is 84.2 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 29,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 190,
    "Question": "What is 86 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 30,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 191,
    "Question": "What is 87.8 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 31,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 192,
    "Question": "What is 89.6 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 32,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 193,
    "Question": "What is 91.4 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 33,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 194,
    "Question": "What is 93.2 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 34,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 195,
    "Question": "What is 95 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 196,
    "Question": "What is 96.8 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 36,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 197,
    "Question": "What is 98.6 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 37,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 198,
    "Question": "What is 100.4 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 38,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 199,
    "Question": "What is 102.2 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 39,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 200,
    "Question": "What is 104 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 201,
    "Question": "What is 105.8 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 41,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 202,
    "Question": "What is 107.6 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 42,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 203,
    "Question": "What is 109.4 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 43,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 204,
    "Question": "What is 111.2 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 44,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 205,
    "Question": "What is 113 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 45,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 206,
    "Question": "What is 114.8 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 46,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 207,
    "Question": "What is 116.6 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 47,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 208,
    "Question": "What is 118.4 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 48,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 209,
    "Question": "What is 120.2 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 49,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 210,
    "Question": "What is 122 degrees F in degrees C",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "C"
  },
  {
    "Number": 211,
    "Question": "What is 5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 41,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 212,
    "Question": "What is 7.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 45.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 213,
    "Question": "What is 10 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 214,
    "Question": "What is 12.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 54.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 215,
    "Question": "What is 15 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 59,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 216,
    "Question": "What is 17.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 63.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 217,
    "Question": "What is 20 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 68,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 218,
    "Question": "What is 22.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 72.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 219,
    "Question": "What is 25 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 77,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 220,
    "Question": "What is 27.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 81.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 221,
    "Question": "What is 30 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 86,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 222,
    "Question": "What is 32.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 90.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 223,
    "Question": "What is 35 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 95,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 224,
    "Question": "What is 37.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 99.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 225,
    "Question": "What is 40 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 104,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 226,
    "Question": "What is 42.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 108.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 227,
    "Question": "What is 45 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 113,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 228,
    "Question": "What is 47.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 117.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 229,
    "Question": "What is 50 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 122,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 230,
    "Question": "What is 52.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 126.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 231,
    "Question": "What is 55 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 131,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 232,
    "Question": "What is 57.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 135.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 233,
    "Question": "What is 60 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 140,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 234,
    "Question": "What is 62.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 144.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 235,
    "Question": "What is 65 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 149,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 236,
    "Question": "What is 67.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 153.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 237,
    "Question": "What is 70 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 158,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 238,
    "Question": "What is 72.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 162.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 239,
    "Question": "What is 75 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 167,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 240,
    "Question": "What is 77.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 171.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 241,
    "Question": "What is 80 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 176,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 242,
    "Question": "What is 82.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 180.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 243,
    "Question": "What is 85 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 185,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 244,
    "Question": "What is 87.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 189.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 245,
    "Question": "What is 90 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 194,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 246,
    "Question": "What is 92.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 198.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 247,
    "Question": "What is 95 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 203,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 248,
    "Question": "What is 97.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 207.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 249,
    "Question": "What is 100 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 212,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 250,
    "Question": "What is 102.5 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 216.5,
    "Units": "F"
  },
  {
    "Number": 251,
    "Question": "What is 105 degrees C in degrees F",
    "Answer": 221,
    "Units": "F"
  }
]
